Hello friends, welcome to Sunil Shetty channel.
If you have not yet subscribed to the channel, then
subscribe to the channel and click on the bell and
click on the notification. So let's move
towards the video. In today's video,
we will talk about it. First of all,
we will check the basic information fundamentals of this company
and after that, there is no
such company.
If you
cannot make money from this market, then you should get
used to them,
after that it will recover and what you did
Swami Bhai, it is possible that you have made 200-300 from there,
hence, in a month, he has given two
percent return. In the last 6 months,
he has given an item of one percent. In the last one
year, he has given a return of 12%.
In the last five years, he has donated 52%.
In 5 years, this company has made almost
50% of your money. But this is a large cap size
company, so it will definitely double your money in 5 years. So,
it has
fallen a lot. So, as it will go up, it is
from the condition of both maximum and five years.
If you invest in these large cap size companies,  If you invest money in this company, then on an
average, your money will be gone in 5 years,
so that I have already told you that this is a
big cap size company, it had made
and the 52 week low was around Rs 1050, the
dividend is the
net profit of this company, 800 crores in 2018,
increased to 1000 crores in 2019, 1200 crores in 2020
and 1400 crores in 2021, if we talk about 1200 crores in 2022, then
1200 crores, so if
we see overall, the net profit of this company has increased from 800 crores to
1200 crores because it is a
very good thing, so we have to look at it overall,
like in 2020 it was 12, then from there it became 1400 in 2021
and in 2022 it fell again and
reached 1200, so this is not seen
in 2019  5200 crores in 2020, 5200 crores
in 2021, 7000 crores in 2021, 600 crores in 2022, it has
increased to 9000 crores, it has more than doubled.
According to this company,
overall it is doing very well,
so the company is doing very well, be it
sales, network show, any
parameter, take potato, share rolling
pattern parameter, which we
will check thoroughly, then the holding of the company
in this company is 48%,
public holding is 22%, the
chart pattern of this company, then
you will never be able to earn money from the market, you will ultimately become bankrupt
and will
exit by selling the share in loss, if you get this
consultation, you will get used to these two phases, rise and fall,
if in these two conditions, if you are
tremendous
and you will not believe that you will get so
much return in that boom, which you did
not even think of and you did
not believe in yourself, just what you have to do for that, keep it in mind.
You don't have to do anything, just
sit quietly in the hall. If there is
an internal issue in the company, if there is
a problem within the company, then
you will definitely have to think about it in that condition. Or if the
company's results are bad, business is
bad, the company's share security is
continuously making profits, then
you will have to see why this is happening.
If you have noticed any such problem
in the company, then it is
right to consider exiting. But if there is
no problem in the company, the company's sales are
increasing, profits are increasing,
reserves are increasing, the company's
balance sheet is quite good, there is no excessive debt,
such a rolling pattern is quite excellent, even
after that you want to buy the company. And
after that, if the person who has seen the company for a few days
sells the company because of such a small thing, then this may seem like a big deal to
you, but this is the truth, the
harsh reality of the share market. So if you want to
make money, then definitely keep this thing in mind.
Other wise, there
is a company, after looking at these parameters, you should invest in this company.  You
can make a mother of this company, it
is also good, it has a lot of potential because the
insurance sector can grow even more in the times to come
because there are
very few people in India who get
insurance done today, but this industry is already
quite grown, there is still a lot left,
so okay friends, if you liked the video then please
like, share and comment on the video and
subscribe to the channel, we will meet
again in the next video, till then
bye-bye thank you.